<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE knimeNode PUBLIC "-//UNIKN//DTD KNIME Node 2.0//EN" "http://www.knime.org/Node.dtd">
<knimeNode icon="../../icons/dna3.png" type="Manipulator">
    <name>Knime To SDF Port</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Convert Knime input to SDF Command Line port.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>The data on the input port is made available for remote 
               execution via the SDF command line nodes.</intro>
        <option name="Field containing molecule data">
            Field in input table that contains the molecule data which will be
            used to generate the molblocks of the sdf file.</option>
        <option name="Local Exchange Directory">
            Path from local host to network directory which is accessible from 
            both: the local computer running Knime as well as the remote computer 
            on which the SDF Commands will be executed.
        </option>
        <option name="Remote Exchange Directory">
            Path from remote host to network directory which is accessible from 
            both: the local computer running Knime as well as the remote computer 
            on which the SDF Commands will be executed.
        </option>
        <option name="SSH Tab">
           <p>Options for configuring the remote execution via ssh.</p>
           
           <p>These options will affect all nodes connected via the command line 
           pipe following the first generator node.</p>
        </option>
        <option name="Pipe Mode">
           Decides if environment variables for production or development mode 
           are loaded prior to remote command execution.
        </option>
        <option name="Remote Directory">
           Directory on remote host in which the ssh execution will take place.
        </option>
        <option name="Error Log File">
           <p>If specified the stderr of this command is written to this local file.
              Specify a full path. Values of flow variable can be inserted using ${varName}.
              This is especially useful on the server.</p>
        </option>
        <option name="Execute in each node">
           <p>If checked each node directly connected to via a command line pipe
           will be executed separately on node execution. A copy of the output 
           data and stderror will be available on the output port and the node 
           view. This is slow but ideal for debugging a pipe.</p>
           <p>If unchecked no execution takes place on each connected command node. 
           Instead you may use an Executer node (cf. consumer folder) to execute 
           the pipe as a whole. The unix command to execute the pipe is available 
           in each output port view.</p>
        </option>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="In-Port name 0">Knime port containing molecule field</inPort>
        <!-- possibly more input ports here-->
        <outPort index="0" name="SDF">Data from input port available on remote host</outPort>
        <!-- possibly more output ports here-->
    </ports>
    <views>
        <view index="0" name="Command Error Output">Error output if single node execution is activated.</view>
    </views>  
</knimeNode>
